{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The center frequency of a band-pass filter is always equal to the", "opta": "bandwidth", "optb": "\u20133 dB frequency", "optc": "bandwidth divided by Q", "optd": "geometric average of the critical frequencies", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The formula  shows that for a given capacitor, if the voltage changes at a constant rate with respect to time, the current will", "opta": "increase", "optb": "decrease", "optc": "be constant", "optd": "decrease logarithmically", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A zero-level detector is a", "opta": "comparator with a sine-wave output", "optb": "comparator with a trip point referenced to zero", "optc": "peak detector", "optd": "limiter", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A digital-to-analog converter is an application of the", "opta": "scaling adder", "optb": "voltage-to-current converter", "optc": "noninverting amplifier", "optd": "adjustable bandwidth circuit", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If the value of resistor Rf in an averaging amplifier circuit is equal to the value of one input resistor divided by the number of inputs, the output will be equal to", "opta": "the average of the individual inputs", "optb": "the inverted sum of the individual inputs", "optc": "the sum of the individual inputs", "optd": "the inverted average of the individual inputs", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If the input to a comparator is a sine wave, the output is a", "opta": "ramp voltage", "optb": "sine wave", "optc": "rectangular wave", "optd": "sawtooth wave", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A basic series regulator has", "opta": "an error detector", "optb": "a load", "optc": "a reference voltage", "optd": "both an error detector and a reference voltage", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A comparator is an example of a(n)", "opta": "active filter", "optb": "current source", "optc": "linear circuit", "optd": "nonlinear circuit", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Initially, the closed-loop gain (Acl) of a Wien-bridge oscillator should be", "opta": "Acl < 3", "optb": "Acl > 3", "optc": "0", "optd": "Acl  1", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In an averaging amplifier, the input resistances are", "opta": "equal to the feedback resistance", "optb": "less than the feedback resistance", "optc": "greater than the feedback resistance", "optd": "unequal", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A triangular-wave oscillator can consist of an op-amp comparator, followed by a(n)", "opta": "differentiator", "optb": "amplifier", "optc": "integrator", "optd": "multivibrator", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The ramp voltage at the output of an op-amp integrator", "opta": "increases or decreases at a linear rate", "optb": "increases or decreases exponentially", "optc": "is always increasing and never decreasing", "optd": "is constant", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A two-pole high-pass active filter would have a roll-off rate of", "opta": "40 dB/decade", "optb": "\u201340 dB/decade", "optc": "20 dB/decade", "optd": "\u201320 dB/decade", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}